well good morning everyone welcome to
大家早上好
this talk thank you for coming can we
这个演讲感谢您的光临
switch to the what doesn't work
切换到不起作用的地方
yeah thank you
是的，谢谢你
all right so welcome to welcome to this
好的，所以欢迎来到这里
code talk thank you for coming
代码交谈谢谢您的光临
this is a talk about lambda expression
这是关于lambda表达式的讨论
free your lambdas it's in fact a replay
释放您的lambda，实际上是重播
I already did last year
我去年已经做过
so if you saw this talk last year it's
因此，如果您去年看过这个演讲，
mostly the same this year this is a
与今年基本相同
tutorial session so we will be starting
辅导课程，所以我们将开始
at the very beginning of lambda
在lambda的一开始
expressions I would not assume that you
表情我不认为你
have any knowledge about writing lambdas
对编写lambda有任何了解
who never wrote lambda expressions in
谁从来没有写过lambda表达式
Java all right and who if you consider
Java没问题，如果考虑的话
yourself as a seasoned lambda expression
作为经验丰富的Lambda表情表达自己
writer okay about the same amount of
作家对相同数量的东西还可以
people so we'll build up on things from
人们，所以我们将继续从
side to side and for example to create
并排，例如创建
patterns that we can't write without and
没有和我们不能写的模式
expression they see this is really the
他们看到这是真的表达
topic of this talk it is really about
这个话题的主题是关于
lambdas and functional interfaces and
Lambda和函数式接口以及
things like that it is not to talk about
诸如此类的事情是不谈论
streams and characters so I will not be
流和字符，所以我不会
covering this topic at all I will use
我将使用所有涉及此主题的内容
numbers in collection streams and
收集流中的数字和
cultures by the way they are available
可用的文化
seats at the front so please if you have
前排座位，如果有的话
an available stick next to you can you
旁边有可用的棍子吗
raise your hand take your pick
举起你的手
alright my name is Josie I live in in
好吧，我叫乔西，我住在
the Paris Area I put just some link here
巴黎地区我在这里放了一些链接
my Twitter account github account I have
我的Twitter帐户github帐户
two open source projects called stream
两个名为stream的开源项目
duties and character GT that you might
可能的职责和角色GT
check if you're interested in and I also
检查您是否有兴趣，我也
have a SlideShare account I'll publish
有我要发布的SlideShare帐户
those lights on my SlideShare account by
我的SlideShare帐户上的那些灯
tonight and also some content on a
今晚还有一些内容
github by the way I'm also a Java
我也是Java的github
champion and the Java work star music
冠军和Java工作明星音乐
before we start I'd like to apologize
在我们开始之前，我要道歉
because from the next two hours you'll
因为从接下来的两个小时开始
have to learn English speaking with the
必须学习英语口语
French accent
法国口音
the alternative would be that I speak
另一种可能是我说
French that probably wouldn't work much
法语可能效果不大
okay so if you have questions to
好吧，如果您有任何疑问要
solutions you raise your hand you shout
解决方案，你举起你的手，你喊
you make yourself heard so that I can
你让自己听到，所以我可以
hear you hear you and see you if you
听到你听到你，看看你是否
don't or if you have questions up to the
否，或者如果您有疑问，
top whatever you can use this hashtag
无论您可以使用此标签如何，
and try to watch it monitor it so that
并尝试观看它对其进行监控，以便
you I can answer you using using Twitter
你我可以用Twitter回答你
okay we're going to begin with very
好吧，我们将从
basic stuff first question what is this
基本的东西第一个问题是什么
code doing this is the easy quiz of the
这样做的代码很容易
day right so this is basically a compare
正确的一天，所以这基本上是一个比较
table okay comparator this is this is
表还可以的比较器，这是这个
Java five code right we could write this
Java 5代码对，我们可以这样写
code in 2004 when Java 5 was released
2004年发布Java 5时编写的代码
and this is a compiler that basically
这基本上是一个编译器
compared to people using the last name I
与使用姓氏I的人相比
want to sort a list of people I can use
想对我可以使用的人进行排序
this comparator this is very basic stuff
这个比较器这是非常基本的东西
two questions do you think this code is
您认为此代码是两个问题
readable no it's not that bad right I
可读的，不是，我还不错
wouldn't say it's very readable but kind
不会说它可读性很强
of okay we use to this code in fact
好的，我们实际上使用了此代码
would you say that this code is robust
你会说这段代码很健壮吗
can it crash yes you can try if p1 is
它会崩溃吗，可以尝试如果p1是
new lore the last name is new
新知识姓氏是新的
I do not check for any kind of new
我不检查任何新的
pointer exceptions so your pointer
指针异常，所以您的指针
exception can be raised using this kind
可以使用这种方法引发异常
of code all right let us make it a
好的代码让我们把它变成
little more complex with this one what
这个稍微复杂一点
does this could do well basically kind
这基本上可以做得很好吗
of does the same thing compares two
做同一件事比较两个
people using the last name and if the
人们使用姓氏，如果
last name is the same it compressed the
姓氏是相同的，它压缩了
first name to sort this list of people
排序此人名单的名字
and if I ask myself is this code
如果我问自己这是代码
readable hmm is it is it more readable
可读性更好吗
than the previous one
比上一个
quite not it's probably less treatable
完全不是，它的治疗性可能较差
why because I have a if in it and we'll
为什么，因为我里面有一个if，我们会
I guess we all know the sonar toolkit
我想我们都知道声纳工具包
there is this cyclomatic complexity
这种循环复杂性
computed by so now and we have increased
现在计算出来，我们增加了
the cyclomatic complexity of this code
该代码的圈复杂度
so yes readability as as decreased a bit
所以是可读性，因为降低了一点
and also robustness because if you p1 is
以及鲁棒性，因为如果p1是
new get last name returns a new value of
新的获取姓氏返回新值
first name right on the new value this
名字就在新值上
code will also throw a null pointer
代码还将抛出一个空指针
exception which is if I want to make it
例外，那就是如果我想做到
robust it will be much more complex and
健壮的它将更加复杂，
much less readable because I will have
可读性差得多，因为我将拥有
all this technical code to check for new
所有这些技术代码以检查是否有新
stuff inside my application code all
我的应用程序代码中的所有东西
right what is this code doing compare
对，这段代码在做什么比较
people using the last name then using
人们使用姓氏，然后使用
the first name and if the last name and
名字，姓氏和
the first name is the same which can
名字是一样的，可以
happen of course compare using the ages
当然会比较使用年龄
yeah
是的
how about readability hmm not that great
可读性不是很好吗
right much much lower I would say that
对得多低，我会说
this is the kind of code was so used to
这是那种代码，习惯了
see in application that we do not really
在应用程序中看到我们并不是真的
need to read it line by line we just
我们需要逐行阅读它
have a global look at it and we see we
放眼全球，我们看到了
understand what it does and so so we
了解它的作用，所以我们
understand what it does yeah and it's
了解它是做什么的，它是
not that robust neither and by the way
既不那么健壮，顺便说一句
since we do not read it line by line we
因为我们不逐行阅读
do not see problems that could be could
没有看到可能的问题
have sneaked in those code yeah you
潜入了这些代码是的，你
check really I will I will fix the code
检查真的我会修复代码
right oh my god I was comparing the last
哦，天哪，我正在比较最后一个
name of the first person with the site
网站的第一人的名字
with the first thing with of the second
与第二件事的第一件事
one did you see but did show it again
您看到了一个，但是又显示了一次
right since we have some kind of
对，因为我们有某种
automatic reading of this code we do not
自动读取此代码，我们不
we give places for sneaky bugs to hide
我们给藏匿偷偷摸摸的虫子的地方
in and there was a bug in this code that
在此代码中存在一个错误
we maybe somebody
我们也许有人
some of you didn't see at first you'd
你们中有些人起初没有看到
better have a very good unit test case
最好有一个很好的单元测试用例
to fix this code alright big to see this
修复此代码好大看这个
bug because you need to have two people
bug，因为您需要两个人
with the same last name and the last
具有相同的姓氏和姓氏
name of the first person has to be lower
第一人称名字必须小写
than the first thing for the second
比第一件事更重要
person to see this so this is typically
看这个的人，所以这通常是
the kind of bug that will make it into
会变成什么样的错误
your production code if you're just
您的生产代码（如果您只是
sorting lists of students or pupil or
排序学生或学生的清单，或
pupils in a classroom it might be okay
教室里的学生可能还可以
but if you are drawing the winner of 1
但是如果您要吸引1的获胜者
million price and some kind of loss we
百万的价格和某种损失
might be in trouble if you do that ok so
如果这样做就可能有麻烦，所以
the problem with this comparator here I
这个比较器的问题在这里我
am really trying to address a very
我真的想解决一个非常
simple and very classical problem I need
我需要的简单而非常经典的问题
to sort a list of people using the last
使用最后一个排序人名单
name their first name and their age and
命名他们的名字和年龄，以及
every time I add a criteria in in this
每次我在此添加条件
in this comparison I increase the
在这个比较中，我增加了
cyclomatic complexity I decrease the
圈复杂度降低了
robustness and I have a terrible mess of
健壮性，我的糟糕透顶
a code that is very hard to fix if there
如果有的话很难修复的代码
are bugs in it so this is exactly what I
是其中的错误，所以这正是我
do not want to do and this is what we
不想做，这就是我们
are going to address using lambda
将使用lambda解决
expressions and patterns with using
表达式和模式与
default beta system basically the code
默认的beta系统基本上是代码
we are going to write is this one which
我们要写的是这个
does the exact same thing as the
做与...完全相同的事情
previous one the difference being if I
上一个不同的是，如果我
add criteria through my comparator I
通过我的比较器我添加标准
will just add method calls so I do not
只会添加方法调用，所以我不
increase socratic complexity and all the
增加了苏格拉底式的复杂性
code that is going to make my competitor
代码将使我的竞争对手
robust that is all the code that will
强大的所有代码
check for null pointer exception and
检查空指针异常并
stuff is pushed in the API code does not
东西被推送到API代码中不
leak in my application code so it does
我的应用程序代码中泄漏，所以它确实
not make my application code any any
不要让我的应用程序代码任何
more complex all right so let us take a
更复杂吧，让我们来
closer look at the comparator basically
仔细看比较器
what we want to do is to sort the
我们要做的是对
strings of a list of strings of
的字符串列表中的字符串
character so that we can create a
角色，以便我们可以创建一个
comparator of string here I'm sorting my
字符串的比较器在这里我正在排序我的
strings using their length instead of
字符串使用其长度而不是
the alphabetical order person the
字母顺序的人
natural order okay so I can create a
自然顺序好，所以我可以创建一个
combat so this is the Java
战斗，所以这是Java
five have to Java 7 way of writing it
五种必须用Java 7编写的方式
and what do I do with this comparator
我该怎么做比较器
the in a nutshell what I want to do is
简而言之，我想做的是
to pass this comparator to salt methods
将此比较器传递给盐方法
so I've got two in the JDK arrays dot
所以我在JDK数组中有两个点
sort and Corrections that sort and those
排序和更正
sort method are going to use this
排序方法将使用此
comparator later on what did we do we
比较器之后我们做了什么
just passed the piece of code as a
刚刚通过了一段代码作为
parameter to a method and this method
方法的参数和此方法
here in this case the salt method we'll
在这种情况下，我们将使用盐法
be using that code later on and several
稍后再使用该代码
times right and why did I use an
正确的时间，为什么我使用
instance of an animist class to do that
万物有灵论者的实例
well just because this is the only way I
好吧，因为这是我唯一的方法
have pass code as a parameter in Java 7
在Java 7中将密码作为参数
if I want to pass code as a parameter in
如果我想将代码作为参数传递给
Java 7 I have to use an instance of
Java 7我必须使用
anonymous class I do not have any other
我没有其他匿名班
solutions to do that with lambda Azam I
lambda Azam I的解决方案
can pass this code precisely as a lambda
可以像lambda一样准确地传递此代码
expression so lambda is basically a way
表达，所以lambda基本上是一种方法
to rewrite this comparator how is the
重写此比较器
lambda returned now I just need to
lambda现在回来了，我只需要
consider that I have a block of
认为我有一个障碍
parameter to the method of this
此方法的参数
comparator here the two strings and a
比较器这里有两个字符串和一个
return statement and the lambda is
返回语句，lambda是
bigger as that I just copy/paste the
更大，因为我只是复制/粘贴
block of parameter draw this little
参数块画得这么少
ASCII art a row using it their sign and
ASCII艺术使用它的符号行
greater than sign this is just LG about
大于标志，这只是LG
the old days of computing right and push
推算的过去
the return statement this is the way and
返回语句是这样的
we're going to see many examples of that
我们将看到许多这样的例子
this is how we write lambdas in general
这就是我们一般编写lambda的方式
the comparator interface becomes in Java
比较器接口变为Java
8 what is called a functional interface
8所谓的函数式接口
what is a functional interface it's an
什么是函数式接口
interface that has only one abstract
只有一个摘要的接口
method this is the most simple
方法，这是最简单的
definition of what a functional
功能定义
interface is the functional interface
接口是函数式接口
may be annotated with this functional
可能带有此功能的注释
interface annotation it's not mandatory
接口注释不是强制性的
it sits
它坐
optional you don't have to do it if you
可选，如果您不必这样做
do it the compiler will tell you at
编译器会告诉您
compile time that is in your IDE and
在IDE中编译时间
we'll see that if this annotated
我们将看到，如果对此进行了注释
interface is indeed functional or not if
接口是否确实起作用，如果
you don't do it then the compiler will
你不这样做，那么编译器会
tell you if you try to implement this
告诉你是否尝试实现这一点
interface using a lambda hey you can do
界面使用lambda嘿你可以做
that because this is not a functional
因为这不是功能
interface so it's just something that is
界面，所以只是
here to help you to helpers it's not
在这里帮助您的助手不是
something that is mandatory by the way
顺便说一句
since it is not mandatory it is also a
由于不是强制性的，因此它也是一个
way to take your old Java let us save
采用旧Java的方式让我们保存
five code in jars and implement it using
罐子中的五个代码，并使用
lambda expression in the Java eight
Java 8中的lambda表达式
parts of your application without having
您的应用程序的一部分而无需
to recombine those so it's also for
重组它们，所以这也是
backward compatibility reasons demo time
向后兼容性原因演示时间
great I love demos but I need my glasses
太棒了，我喜欢演示，但我需要戴眼镜
okay it's the phone big enough yeah if
好吧，电话够大的，如果
you if you can't read the code just just
你，如果你不能只看代码
tell me I can yeah you do that while I'm
告诉我，我可以，你可以在我
doing that if you can raise your hand if
如果可以举手的话
you have an empty seat near you because
您附近有空位，因为
there are people
那里有人
is it better yeah is it now okay fine so
是不是更好，现在可以了吗
this is a list okay once a list and we
这是一个列表，一旦列表，我们可以
are going to use this this new for each
将要为每个使用此新
method defined on the interval interface
在间隔接口上定义的方法
that allows that takes a long that that
这需要很长的时间
is going to be applied on the list and
将被应用到列表中，
here this for each method takes a non de
在这里，每种方法都需要一个非de
expression as a parameter and the
表达式作为参数，
question I'm asking myself is how can I
我问自己的问题是我怎么能
write this lambda expression this lambda
写这个lambda表达式这个lambda
expression - right along the expression
表达式-沿着表达式
you need to identify what is the
您需要确定什么是
interface you need to implement it has
您需要实现的接口
to be a functional interface and what is
成为函数式接口，什么是
the abstract method of this interface so
这个接口的抽象方法
this is what I'm going to do for that I
这就是我要做的
can navigate to the fridge method oh
可以导航到冰箱的方法哦
okay it's a default method to see that
好的，这是一种默认方法
this method takes a consumer as a
这种方法将消费者视为
parameter I'm going to watch this
参数，我要看这个
consumer interface this is indeed a
消费者界面，这确实是一个
functional interface so by definition it
函数式接口，按定义
has only one abstract method which is
只有一种抽象方法是
the accept method here how can i
我这里的接受方法
implement this abstract method using a
使用以下方法实现此抽象方法
lambda well as we saw in the slide I
就像我们在幻灯片中看到的那样
just need to copy paste the block of
只需要复制粘贴的块
parameter let me do that draw this
参数让我做得出这个
little old fashioned hour like ask yacht
小小的老式小时像问游艇
and return void so if I just want to
然后返回void，所以如果我只想
return what I can write it like that
返回我可以这样写的东西
this is a block of code that returns
这是返回的代码块
void so at least it should compile as
无效，因此至少应编译为
long as I say that this T is in fact the
只要我说这个T实际上是
string and indeed this code does compile
字符串，实际上此代码确实可以编译
the lambda I just wrote using this
我刚刚用这个写的lambda
method is an implementation of the
方法是
consumer interface of course it doesn't
消费者界面当然不是
do much so let us try to be smart here
做很多事情，让我们在这里变得聪明
I'm going to print out
我要打印出来
this string of character okay that I
这串字符好吗，我
call t enough s and if I run this code
叫足够t，如果我运行这段代码
okay it just print out the content of
好吧，它只是打印出内容
the list by the way I do not have to
列表，我不必
write the type of the parameter here
在这里写参数的类型
because the compiler is smart enough
因为编译器足够聪明
since he knows the method I am
因为他知道我的方法
implementing it is smart enough to guess
实现它足够聪明，可以猜测
the type of T the compiler knows that
T的类型，编译器知道
this is in fact a string of character so
这实际上是一个字符串，所以
you see that it's not that complex to
您会发现它并不那么复杂
right-handers let us take another
右撇子让我们再拿一个
example with another functional
另一个功能的例子
interface which is the iterable
接口是可迭代的
interface let us write an iterable
界面让我们写一个可迭代的
string okay let us take a look at this
字符串好吧，让我们看看这个
interval interface this little interface
间隔接口这个小接口
is not annotated with functional
没有用功能注释
interface but it has only one abstract
接口，但只有一个摘要
method which returns an iterator does
返回迭代器的方法
not take any parameter let us implement
不带任何参数让我们实施
that method using a lambda expression
使用lambda表达式的方法
copy/paste the block of code it's an
复制/粘贴代码块
empty block of code draw this little
空的代码块画了一点
arrow stuff and return an iterator so I
箭头的东西，并返回一个迭代器，所以我
could well return the null value this
很可能返回null值
code should compile and indeed it does
代码应该编译，确实可以
compile now I should be returning of
现在编译我应该返回
course a real iterator I've got a list
当然有一个真正的迭代器，我有一个清单
of strings here so I can just take the
在这里，所以我可以把
iterator from this list of string and
来自此字符串列表的迭代器，并且
this is an implementation of the
这是一个实现
iterable interface I can check that just
可迭代的界面，我可以检查一下
by passing this iterable to this for
通过将此迭代传递给
each pattern and print the result like
每个图案并像打印结果一样
that it indeed prints out all the
它确实打印出了所有
elements of the interface of the other
其他接口的元素
list we can take one last example with
我们可以列举最后一个例子
another interface the executor interface
另一个接口执行器接口
executor
执行者
this executor interface is also a
这个执行者界面也是
functional interface it has only one
函数式接口只有一个
abstract method once again it's not
抽象方法再次不是
annotated with functional interface but
带有函数式接口，但
we can still work with it it takes a run
我们仍然可以使用它，但需要运行
a ball as a parameter so let us take
一个球作为参数，让我们来
this block of code and copy paste it
此代码块并复制粘贴
draw this little arrow and it returns
画这个小箭头，它会返回
void so I can implement it using this
无效，所以我可以使用它来实现
dump
倾倒
order and this should compile and indeed
秩序，这应该编译，的确
it does now what I need to do is of
现在我要做的是
course execute this run a ball so I
当然执行这个跑球，所以我
could write this command ran for
可以写这个命令运行
instance to execute this run of all I'm
实例来执行我​​所有的运行
going to call this executor number
要拨打这个执行人号码
because of course it's not it's
因为当然不是
executing the runnable in the current
在当前执行可运行
thread which is not what an executor
不是执行者的线程
should do if I want to create another
如果我想创建另一个应该怎么做
executor that can that I can call smart
我可以称之为聪明的执行者
executor and run this task in another
执行器并在另一个中运行此任务
thread I could use these executors
线程我可以使用这些执行程序
executors actually matado new or a
遗嘱执行人实际上matado new还是
single thread executor execute this
单线程执行器执行此
command as a parameter so that you can
命令作为参数，以便您可以
see all right we can test this code for
好的，我们可以测试此代码
that I need a runnable this would be my
我需要一个可运行的，这将是我的
task by the way if I check the runnable
顺便说一句，如果我检查可运行
interface guess what relays are sewn
界面猜测缝制了什么继电器
functional interface so I can implement
函数式接口，因此我可以实施
a runnable using a lambda let us do that
使用lambda的runnable让我们做到这一点
what does it take takes no parameter and
它不需要什么参数，并且
doesn't return anything so I should be
不返回任何东西，所以我应该
able to implement it like that
能够像这样实现
looks like JavaScript right okay so this
看起来像JavaScript没关系，所以这
is this is a random compiled
这是一个随机的废话吗
and it would work of course it wouldn't
它当然会工作，但不会
do much but it would work so what I can
做很多事，但是会起作用，所以我可以
do is appoint for instance just print
做是任命，例如只是打印
out the thread Amina I am in thread read
退出线程Amina我正在线程中读取
current read something like that and
目前读这样的东西，
then dump executors execute this task
然后转储执行程序执行此任务
and do it again with my smart executor
然后用我聪明的执行者再做一次
if I run this code indeed the first one
如果我运行此代码，确实是第一个
was executed in the main thread which is
在主线程中执行
which is exactly what is expected and
这正是所期望的
the second one executed in one thread
第二个在一个线程中执行
one which is the thread of my executor
这是我的执行人的线程
service I need to shut this by hand
服务我需要手动关闭
because I did not shut down this mod
因为我没有关闭这个模组
executable which is of course very wrong
可执行文件，这当然是非常错误的
don't use this kind of code in
不要在
production just one note if I take this
如果我接受这一点，生产只是一个音符
code here as an iterable and copy-paste
在此处作为可迭代和复制粘贴的代码
there
那里
I have no if you can see it I have a
如果您能看到我没有，我有一个
compiler
编译器
oops I have a compiler error this code
糟糕，我有一个编译器错误此代码
does not compile why because the
不编译为什么，因为
compiler has to know at compile time the
编译器必须在编译时知道
type of lambda expression I am writing
我正在写的lambda表达式的类型
so lambda should be either affected to a
因此，lambda应该要么受到
field or variable will be sent as a
字段或变量将作为
parameter or be written by by a method I
参数或由方法I编写
cannot take a lambda as it is put it
不能像输入的那样接受lambda
just like that in this code and hope
就像这段代码和希望一样
that it would work for instance if I
例如，如果我
just copy paste this code here like that
只是复制粘贴此代码像这样
put it into parenthesis and code like
放在括号和类似的代码中
that I will have a compiler error
我会有一个编译器错误
because the compiler cannot guess what
因为编译器无法猜测
is the type of the lambda of just
是公正的lambda的类型
written I need to put it in a variable
写的我需要把它放在一个变量中
for that
为了那个原因
I'm going to swim to this go alright
我要去游泳了
alright let's continue so writing along
好吧，让我们继续，所以写
down in a chair is a matter of finding
坐在椅子上是一个发现的问题
you what interface what functional
你什么接口什么功能
interface I am implementing and in that
我正在实现的界面
interface to identify which method I am
界面来确定我是哪种方法
implementing and when I have identified
实施以及何时确定
that it's a matter of taking the block
这是一个障碍的问题
of parameter understanding what should
参数了解什么
be returned and be smart and put the
返回并变得聪明，把
right code in the body of them so
在他们身上正确的代码
basically a method lambda is just a
基本上方法lambda只是一个
method that I can pass as a parameter in
我可以作为参数传递的方法
my code in my application there is
我的应用程序中的代码有
something kind of where that just happen
发生什么事的地方
ah yes this funny syntax is called a
啊，是的，这个有趣的语法叫做
method reference we are going to see
我们将要看到的方法参考
that in a minute that is the for each
在一分钟内，每个
method is defined on the iterable
方法在迭代器上定义
interface this is the code that we just
接口，这就是我们刚才的代码
wrote here right and has been added in
正确地写在这里，并已添加到
Java 8 so adding a method in an
Java 8，因此在
interface of course implies that all the
接口当然意味着所有
implementations of that interface should
该接口的实现
be updated for the code to work and of
更新代码以使其正常工作
course it would have meant to refactor
当然，这本来意味着重构
all the collection API and all the
所有集合API和所有
existing implementations of iterable
可迭代的现有实现
interval is the root interface of all
interval是所有根接口
the collection yard so so it would have
收集场，所以它将有
required to update all the code around
需要更新所有代码
which would not have been possible of
这是不可能的
course it would have broken the backward
当然它会打破落后
compatibility of the correction
校正的兼容性
framework which is not possible so now
现在不可能的框架
go in Java to do this kind of thing so
用Java去做这样的事情
the way interfaces work if you have an
如果您有一个接口，接口的工作方式
empty seat near you can you raise your
您附近的空位可以举起吗
hand again please comment can have a
再次举手请发表评论
seat downtown stay at the back so the
座落在市中心，所以在后面
way interfaces work have been modified
接口工作方式已被修改
in Java 8 and for each method is in fact
在Java 8中，实际上每种方法
a default method what is a default
默认方法什么是默认方法
method it's a regular method added in an
方法这是一个常规方法
interface along with its implementation
接口及其实现
it just had the default
它只是具有默认值
keyword in front of in front of it right
在它前面的关键词
and there's something it's it is just a
有一点就是
plain regular method very very easy to
普通的常规方法非常非常容易
understand the this default method is a
了解此默认方法是
normal method put in an interface what
普通方法放在一个接口里是什么
is new is that we can now have
新的是，我们现在可以拥有
implementations in an interface was not
接口中的实现不是
possible up to Java 7 but it is a new
可能直到Java 7为止，但这是一个新的
concept of interface it is not a new
接口的概念不是一个新概念
concept of method it is just a plain old
方法的概念只是一个普通的旧
regular method as well used to write
常规方法也用于编写
down this is how it has been sold to us
下来这就是它卖给我们的方式
when Java 8 was released almost 4 years
当Java 8发布近4年时
ago but it is much much more than that
以前，但远不止于此
and and I guess that in a few years from
而且我想从那以后的几年
now people will not be learning that
现在人们将不会学习
default method have been introduced for
引入了默认方法
the backward compatibility bla bla bla
向后兼容性bla bla bla
they will learn something else and by
他们会学到其他东西
the way we can also put public static
我们也可以将公共静态方法
methods in Java 8 in interfaces which is
接口中Java 8中的方法
new and in Java 9 will be able to put
Java 9中的新功能
private static methods to so a function
私有静态方法如此功能
will isn't so now in an interface I can
现在我可以在界面中这样
have abstract methods default methods
有抽象方法默认方法
and static methods only abstract methods
和静态方法只有抽象方法
count to tell if an interfaces is a
数出一个接口是否是一个
functional interface or not default and
函数式接口或不是默认界面
static method do not count which is nice
静态方法不算哪个好
because it means that I will be able to
因为这意味着我将能够
put abstract methods in function
将抽象方法放入函数中
interface and add a bunch of of default
界面并添加一堆默认值
method which is what I'm going to do
我要做的方法
another what are we going to do I'm
另一个，我们要做什么
going to close this tab
要关闭此标签
I don't need it anymore
我不再需要了
I prepare the two interfaces we are
我准备了两个接口
going to use now
现在要使用
first the my consumer interface which is
首先是我的消费者界面
a mimic of a consumer interface from the
用户界面的模仿
java.util package that we're going to
我们将要使用的java.util包
talk about in a minute and we are going
稍等一下，我们要去
to do stuff with it what is a consumer
用它做东西是什么消费者
it has only one method this is the
它只有一种方法是
system dot out dot println we've been
我们已经去过系统dot out dot println
using with the Forex method a few
与Forex方法一起使用
minutes ago right so I'm going to create
分钟前，所以我要创建
a first consumer consumer string for
的第一个消费者消费者字符串
instance are eating yeah
实例在吃呀
yeah this is eating yes okay and if I'm
是的，这是吃得好，如果我
calling the accept method of this my
叫这个我的接受方法
consumer interface eating chicken and I
消费者界面和我一起吃鸡肉
run this code it just displays eating
运行此代码，它只会显示进餐
chicken which is nice I'm going to write
我要写的鸡真好
a second consumer drinking right there's
第二个喝酒的人
almost the same
差不多一样
drinking I'm going to run it drinking
喝酒，我要去喝酒
drinking except coffee okay chicken and
除了咖啡还可以喝鸡肉和
drinking coffee now suppose I will I
现在我想喝咖啡
want to create another consumer eating
想要创造另一个消费者的饮食
and drinking I want in fact to compose
实际上我想组成的喝酒
those two consumers into one just one
那两个消费者合而为一
and for that I would like to write this
为此，我想写这个
kind of code and then drinking okay of
某种代码，然后饮用
course this and then method doesn't work
当然这然后方法不起作用
on it and then I need to create it how
在上面，然后我需要创建它
can i implement this kind of thought
我可以实施这种想法吗
this is very basic pattern right I won't
这是非常基本的模式，我不会
just to create a consumer that will be
只是为了创建一个消费者
the combination of the first consumer
第一个消费者的组合
and that the chaining of the first
并且第一个链接
consumer and then the second consumer
消费者，然后是第二消费者
what if I check this method and then
如果我检查此方法然后
what is this method it is a method
这是什么方法
called
叫
only eating object here so it's an
这里只吃东西，所以
instance method of the eating object so
饮食对象的实例方法
I have on this my consume interface
我有这个我的消费界面
another method called and then of course
另一个方法称为然后
that is going to take something and
这将需要一些东西，
return something
还东西
what does it take as a parameter it
它作为参数是什么
takes a my consumer and what does it
带我的消费者，这是什么
return them returns another micron Shiva
返回他们返回另一个微米湿婆
do that I take my consumer as a
这样做，我将我的消费者视为
parameter and return my consumer object
参数并返回我的消费者对象
if I write it like that this interface
如果我这样写的话
is perfectly legal but of course you
是完全合法的，但您当然可以
have the problems because I have an
有问题，因为我有一个
interface that has to abstract methods
具有抽象方法的接口
it's not a functional interface anymore
它不再是函数式接口
so it does not compile I cannot
所以它不能编译我不能
implement this interface using a lambda
使用lambda实现此接口
by the way if I add
顺便说一句，如果我添加
this functional interface annotation
该函数式接口注释
here you see that this time the the
在这里，您看到这次
compiler will be raised on the interface
编译器将在接口上引发
itself since I have two abstract method
本身，因为我有两种抽象方法
and this interface is not a functional
而且此接口不起作用
interface anymore so this adding this
接口了，所以这个添加了这个
method as an abstract method is not the
方法作为抽象方法不是
way to go but remember I can add default
要走的路，但请记住我可以添加默认值
methods on Maya fractional interface on
Maya分数接口上的方法
any kind of interface by the way so let
顺便说一下，任何一种界面
us make this interface default this time
我们这次将这个界面设为默认界面
I need to provide an implementation and
我需要提供一个实现
you see that this code does compile my
您会看到这段代码确实编译了我的
interface is functional again and of
界面再次正常工作
course I can implement it using lambda
当然我可以用lambda实现
expressions so now what should I do in
表达式，所以现在我该怎么做
this and then method what I need to
然后我需要的方法
return is a my consumer okay my consumer
回报是我的消费者，好吧，我的消费者
is a functional interface so it can be
是一个函数式接口，因此可以
implemented using a lambda what is this
使用lambda实现这是什么
lambda well just need to apply the exact
lambda很好，只需要应用确切的
same method with it
同样的方法
we applied previously identify the only
我们以前应用过的唯一
abstract method of the my consumer
我的消费者的抽象方法
interface then copy/paste the block of
界面，然后复制/粘贴
parameter draw this little funny right
参数画这个小有趣的权利
stuff and return okay boy so if I write
东西，还好男孩，所以如果我写
it like that it should compile and
它应该编译并
indeed it does compile this it this is a
的确确实编译了它，这是一个
consumer alright so now I need to be a
消费者好，所以现在我需要成为一个
little smarter what I expect here is to
我期望这里要聪明一点
first consumer the object I am going to
第一个消费者我要去的对象
pass to this compost consumer to consume
传递给这个堆肥消费者
them with the first consumer the
他们与第一个消费者
consumer I am in this consumer and then
消费者我在这个消费者中，然后
the consumer passed as a parameter so
消费者作为参数传递，因此
let us do that when I am in this code I
当我在这段代码中时，让我们这样做
am in an instance of a consumer so I can
在一个消费者的实例中，所以我可以
call this accept
称之为接受
of T maybe print out something like that
的T可能会打印出类似的内容
and then and then consume this T object
然后再消耗这个T对象
with the other consumer passed as a
与其他消费者通过
parameter right now if I eating and
如果我现在吃东西，
drinking eating and drinking accept good
喝酒吃喝接受好
food okay I'm not really drinking good
食物还可以，我喝的不是很好
food but anyway it will just work like
食物，但是无论如何它会像
that my default method implemented
我的默认方法已实现
invite the chaining of the to consumers
邀请链接到消费者
this and other passed as a parameter so
这个和其他作为参数传递，所以
you see that using this kind of default
您会看到使用这种默认设置
method allows us to invite opens up all
方法允许我们邀请打开所有
the way of new patterns that is
新模式的方式是
composing lambda expressions and this is
组成lambda表达式，这是
what we are going to do until the end of
直到年底我们将要做的事情
this of this session let us take another
本届会议的这个让我们再来
example with the with another functional
与另一个功能的示例
interface from the JDK that I have
我拥有的JDK接口
mimicked here any available seats
在这里模仿任何可用的座位
alright so it might predict eight
好吧，所以它可以预测八
interface once again it is a mimic of
界面再次是模仿
the predicate interface available on J
J上可用的 Predicate 接口
in the JDK and we are going to write
在JDK中，我们将要编写
some some stuff with it
一些东西
so my we are going to take for instance
所以我要举个例子
of my predicate of Austria my particular
我的奥地利谓语
string you know not new right and it
字符串，你知道不是新的权利，它
will just check if this this given
只会检查这个给定
string of character or not and I'm going
字符串是否存在，我要去
to take another one shorter and then all
再花一个短一点然后全部
right it's it will be s that length
对，就是那样的长度
length less than ten those are two
长度小于十的那是两个
predicates and a natural way to combine
谓词和自然的组合方式
predicates to compose predicates is for
谓词组成谓词是为了
instance two to use and meet the other
实例二使用和见面
so not new dot and shorter than ten
所以不是新点，并且少于十
should also be a predicate a string that
也应该是谓词字符串，
I'm going to call let's say p1 okay so
我要打电话说p1好吧
once again I am facing the exact same
我再次面对着完全一样的
problem as the the composition of my to
问题作为我的组成
consumers Here I am and method that is
消费者在这里，我的方法是
an instance method of the not new object
不是新对象的实例方法
so it is an instant method into my
所以这是我的即时方法
predicate interface it cannot be another
Predicate 接口，不能是另一个
abstract method because if it was it
抽象方法，因为如果是这样
would break the functional interface
会破坏函数式接口
stuff so I'm going to make it a default
东西，所以我将其设为默认值
method and then this and then method
方法，然后这个，然后方法
takes a predicate as a parameter and
以谓词为参数，
returns also a predicate let us do that
还返回一个谓词，让我们做到这一点
so return the predicate takes a
所以返回谓词需要一个
predicate as a parameter so if I just
谓词作为参数，所以如果我只是
return near here it should at least
返回这里至少应该
compile it does not oh yes sorry this is
编译它不会哦，对不起，这是
just and here so now it should compile
只是在这里所以现在应该编译
thank you all right so what do I return
好的，谢谢，我该怎么办
and my predicate how do i implement
和我的谓词我该如何实施
predicates using a lambda this lambda is
使用lambda的谓词，此lambda是
an implementation of the test method
测试方法的实现
that is here always the same process of
在这里总是相同的过程
creating this lambda so I'm just going
创建这个lambda，所以我要去
to copy paste the block of parameter I
复制粘贴参数I的块
need to return a boolean so if I just
需要返回一个布尔值，所以如果我只是
return true with a first step to see at
第一步返回true返回
least that could compile indeed it does
至少可以编译确实可以
and this boolean should be the logical
这个布尔值应该是合乎逻辑的
end of the predicate I am inner using
我内部使用的谓词结尾
this test method
此测试方法
and the predicate passed as a parameter
谓词作为参数传递
so here is just this test of T and test
所以这只是T和测试的测试
we can test this code p1 the test stable
我们可以测试这段代码p1测试稳定
printer n test with
打印机n测试
from this code oops
从此代码哎呀
sorry
抱歉
nine-nine
九九
yes one reason this is a pretty cake
是的，这是一个漂亮的蛋糕
oh yeah right sorry yes that's right
哦，是的，对不起，是的，是的
okay thank you
好的谢谢
what happens uh okay so this what like
会发生什么，好吧，这就像
that what happens if I pass no as a
如果我不通过，会发生什么
parameter here this is interesting if I
参数在这里，如果我很有趣
run this code of course oops
当然运行这段代码
I'm going to if I run this code of
我要运行以下代码
course I have a null pointer exception
当然我有一个空指针异常
but the interesting point is where does
但有趣的一点是在哪里
this no pointer exception comes from you
这个没有指针的异常来自你
see that it comes from inside the lambda
看到它来自lambda内部
which is here if all there is now this
如果现在有这个就在这里
code is going to throw the null pointer
代码将抛出空指针
exception as long as the first test is
只要第一个测试是例外
true so it means that if I do not call
是真的，这意味着如果我不打电话
this code this code is going to run
此代码此代码将要运行
perfectly well you see so if I create a
很好，您知道，所以如果我创建一个
predicate with an other that is new I
谓词与另一个是新的我
have a corrupted lambda expression that
lambda表达式已损坏
is going to that is bound to throw a
要去那肯定会抛出一个
null pointer exception somewhere but
空指针异常在某处但是
this new pointer exception will not be
这个新的指针异常将不会
thrown at the creation of the lambda but
在创建lambda时抛出，但是
when I will be using this come down in
当我将使用它下来
my application so if I pass this lambda
我的申请，所以如果我通过这个lambda
to some kind of other module in my
到我的某种其他模块
application and this standard is used in
应用程序，该标准用于
ten days from now this null pointer
从现在起十天
exception is going to be thrown much
异常将被抛出很多
later than the moment where this lambda
迟于此lambda的时刻
is created and this will make an kind of
被创建，这将使一种
impossible to fix
无法修复
but because the the stacktrace I will
但是因为我的堆栈跟踪
have will give me the place where the
有给我的地方
lambda is used when the bug is in fact
实际上存在错误时使用lambda
at the place where the lambda is created
在创建lambda的地方
so if I want to prevent this kind of
所以如果我想防止这种情况
stuff I need to throw the null pointer
我需要抛出空指针的东西
exception at the lambda creation that is
Lambda创建中的异常是
here now if I run this code again
现在在这里，如果我再次运行此代码
of course the null pointer exception is
当然，空指针异常是
thrown when I try to build a lambda and
当我尝试构建lambda时抛出
this is a pattern we really need to use
这是我们真正需要使用的模式
because we do not want to have
因为我们不想拥有
impossible to fix bugs in our
无法修复我们的错误
applications this is a an application of
应用程序这是一个应用程序
a very old principle in exception and
一个非常古老的原则，例外
Lane we chill which is fail fast fail
车道让我们畏惧失败
first if I know that this one is going
首先，如果我知道这将要发生
to be cluttered I throw a minor point
混乱不堪，我只说了一点
exception right now by the way this is
现在是这样的异常
what I should have been doing here also
我也应该在这里做什么
objects
对象
yeah yeah
是啊
yeah you mean if I call and then and
是的，你的意思是如果我打电话然后
then and then and then it will continue
然后然后然后它将继续
to work no problem and then
工作没问题，然后
yeah lutely you can't you can change
是的，行不通，你不能改变
consumers you can chain as many
您可以连锁的消费者
consumers as you need and you can
您需要的消费者，您可以
compose as many predicates as you need
根据需要组成任意多个谓词
with and and create and all methods or
与和创建所有方法或
this kind of thing yeah well you mean in
这种事情是的，你的意思是
Nicole yeah yes but this is this is what
妮可，是的，但这就是这个
I've written if this is what I need it's
我写了这是否是我需要的
okay you see this is a consumer well
好吧，你看到这是一个消费者
there's nothing you can do to prevent
您无法采取任何预防措施
that from within the intent method
在意图方法中
because you don't know okay this is a
因为你不知道这是一个
consumer I could put that in a variable
消费者，我可以把它放在一个变量中
and this is just a regular consumers I'm
这只是我的老顾客
just calling and then method on the
只是调用然后在
regular consumer so there is no way
普通消费者，所以没有办法
within the Endon method for me to know
在Endon方法中让我知道
that in fact the consumer I I am in is
实际上，消费者II在
itself a composition of other consumers
本身就是其他消费者的组成
we can also predicate for instance we
我们也可以断言我们
can also create other default methods
也可以创建其他默认方法
for instance the p1 the shorter than 10
例如p1短于10
I could say alright I want I want to
我可以说我想我想要
implement the negate operator on the
实现否定运算符
consumer the this negate operator is
消费者，这个否定运算符是
also a default method but this time it
也是默认方法，但是这次
does not take any parameter okay so let
不需要任何参数，所以让
us write it default it returns a my
我们写它默认它返回一个我的
predicate of T call negate and does not
T调用谓词否定，并且不
take any parameter okay so what should I
可以接受任何参数，那我该怎么办
return now once again this is a
现在再次返回，这是一个
predicate so I copy/paste the block of
谓词，所以我复制/粘贴
parameters here little arrow and this
参数在这里小箭头和这个
should return
应该回来
the negation of the testing of T which I
我对T测试的否定
can write just like it so you see that
可以这样写，所以你看到
default method allowed us to implement
默认方法允许我们实现
composition and manipulations of
的组成和操作
functions as expressions okay so we've
可以用作表达式，所以我们已经
got functional interfaces to write on
有可写的函数式接口
that expressions we have default methods
那些表达式我们有默认方法
to compose them we also have a static
组成它们，我们还有一个静态的
method that can be used as factories and
可以用作工厂的方法
we're going to see that on further
我们将进一步看到
examples what what the idea is to give
实例给出什么想法
to our code the better readability
对我们的代码更好的可读性
essentially because we are moving some
基本上是因为我们正在移动一些
part of the technical code especially
特别是技术规范的一部分
the the null pointer handling to the API
对API的空指针处理
instead of having them having that code
而不是让他们拥有该代码
inside our application code this is this
在我们的应用程序代码中，这是
is what leads to better readability and
是什么导致更好的可读性和
also better robustness because we can
更好的鲁棒性，因为我们可以
check for all the exceptions inside
检查里面的所有异常
inside our code and it also gives better
在我们的代码中，它也提供了更好的
performances I will not be covering that
表演我不会讲
point but if you're interested in that
点，但如果您对此感兴趣
there is a very interesting talk by
有一个非常有趣的谈话
Brian gates called lambda peek under the
布赖恩·盖茨（Brian Gates）在
hood available on YouTube we have I
YouTube上的引擎盖，我们有我
mentioned the several time the my
提到了几次我的
consumer and my predicate which are in
消费者和我的谓词
fact mimics of the consumer and
消费者的事实模仿和
predicate functional interfaces
谓词函数式接口
available in the GDK in fact i've got
实际上我已经在GDK中找到了
four big categories of functional
功能的四大类
interfaces in this Java util function
此Java util函数中的接口
package the consumer the supplier the
包装消费者，供应商
function and the predicate we will see
函数和谓词，我们将看到
examples of suppliers and functions for
供应商示例和功能
the examples those are the most basic
这些是最基本的例子
implementations of those functional
这些功能的实现
interface interfaces of consumer take
消费者采取的接口
something does not return anything the
什么不返回任何东西
supplier does not take anything and
供应商不采取任何行动，
reach on something the function takes an
达到功能需要
object of a given type and returns an
给定类型的对象，并返回
object
宾语
and the predicate is a special kind of
谓词是一种特殊的
function that returns a boolean
返回布尔值的函数
I can also well those are more elaborate
我也可以说那些更详尽
example that and I've also have a fifth
例如，我还有第五个
lambda expression where functional
Lambda表达式在哪里起作用
interface that fits nicely I think in
我认为合适的界面
this in this set which is the runnable
在这个集合中这是可运行的
interface a runnable interface is not
接口不是可运行的接口
new it has been here from very early
新的，从很早就到这里了
days of the GDK and it's something that
GDK的日子，那是
doesn't take anything and does not
不带任何东西，也不带
return anything things think about the
返回任何事情的思考
logger for instance basically a logger
记录器例如基本上是记录器
it can be modeled as a rainbow let us go
它可以被建模为彩虹让我们走
back to our comparator example we are
回到我们的比较器示例
going to write a comparator of people
要写一个人的比较器
and for that we are going to use a
为此，我们将使用
lambda expression and then sorry
lambda表达式，然后对不起
anonymous class and then along the
匿名课程，然后
expression it's demo time again okay we
表达它再次是演示时间，好吧，我们
need to close all this stuff alright
需要关闭所有这些东西
play with comparators so I've got a my
与比较器一起玩，所以我有一个
comparator interface which is a mimic of
比较器接口，类似于
the real compare to interface all right
真正的比较界面还可以
I'm going to play with it and I also
我要去玩，我也
have a person class which is a basic bin
有一个人类，这是一个基本的箱
with three properties first name last
具有三个属性的名字姓氏
name and age I'm going to play with that
我将使用的名称和年龄
so let us create my comparator a person
所以让我们创建一个比较器的人
I'm going to call it CMP one new my
我将其称为CMP新产品
competitor yes if I do not support this
竞争对手是，如果我不支持这一点
person we are going to implement it real
我们要真正实现的人
quick right person p1 and person P 2 and
快速正确的人p1和人P 2以及
what I want to do is the following I
我想做的是以下我
want to first I want to p1 take the last
想先，我想先p1
name
名称
this is last name here and p2 that get
这是这里的姓氏，p2
us name this is last name too
我们也叫姓氏
and then I would just want to return the
然后我只想返回
comparison of last name one with a
姓氏与
lasting two this is my comparison now if
持续两个，这是我现在的比较
I take a closer look at this code what I
我仔细看看这段代码我
can do here is extract that to a method
这里可以做的就是将其提取为一种方法
right and if I do that I can see they in
是的，如果我这样做，我可以看到他们
fact my comparator here only depends on
实际上我的比较器仅取决于
this method that is if I want to compare
如果我想比较这种方法
people using their first name what I
人们用他们的名字我
need to do is change its code and the
需要做的是更改其代码，
rest of the code is the same so the
其余代码相同，因此
comparator have written in fact depends
比较器实际上已经写取决于
on the method well this is nice because
在方法上，这很好，因为
I know that with long down with London's
我知道与伦敦的
I can pass methods as parameters so what
我可以将方法作为参数传递
I need to do is to transform this method
我要做的就是转换这种方法
in a lambda and then I will be able to
在lambda中，然后我将能够
create a comparator just by passing risk
仅仅通过冒险就可以创建一个比较器
lambda as a parameter to some kind of
lambda作为某种参数的
factory method for instance okay what
例如工厂方法好吗
does this method do it takes a person
这种方法需要一个人吗
and return a string of characters takes
并返回一个字符串
an object returns an object from another
一个对象从另一个对象返回一个对象
type the model for therefore that
为此键入模型
functional interface which is the model
函数式接口是模型
for that is the function that takes an
因为那是需要一个
object precisely in return another
恰好相反的对象
object of another type so let us write
另一种类型的对象，让我们写
this function
这个功能
it takes a person returns a string I'm
我需要一个人返回一个字符串
going to call it no last name okay it
要叫它没有姓好吗
takes a person P if I found if I have
如果发现我有一个人P
trouble implementing that I can just
实施困难，我只能
navigate to this and copy paste whatever
导航到此并复制粘贴任何内容
I need from this applied method here I'm
我需要这种应用的方法
going to do it directly takes a person P
直接去做需要一个人P
and called get last name right now that
并立即呼叫获取姓氏
I have this functional to transform this
我有这个功能来改变这个
p1 into last name one what I need to do
p1变成姓氏我需要做什么
is call last name and apply it to p1 and
是呼叫姓氏并将其应用于p1和
do the same here
在这里做同样的事情
last name sorry last name apply for some
姓抱歉姓申请一些
p2 here
p2在这里
I do not need this method anymore and
我不再需要这种方法了
now my code only depends on a kind of
现在我的代码只取决于一种
object it's not really an object but let
对象不是一个真正的对象，而是让
us call it like that which is this one
我们这样称呼它
and I see that in fact all this code if
我看到实际上所有这些代码如果
I put it in a method yes I can convert
我把它放在一个方法中，我可以转换
it if I put in a method only depends on
如果我放入一个方法，它仅取决于
this last name here by the way I'm going
这是我要去的姓氏
to to make it run the expression all the
使它全部运行表达式
IDS can do that extract this and this is
IDS可以提取出来，这是
this is let us make it too long the
这让我们把它弄得太长了
expression okay it as I have extracted
表达好吧，因为我已经提取了
this code into a static method which is
将此代码转换为静态方法
a factory method that takes a function
具有功能的工厂方法
and that returns the comparator written
然后返回比较器写入
as a lambda expression so this method
作为lambda表达式，因此此方法
called extract Erdem since it is a
称为提取物Erdem，因为它是
factory method and since I am allowed to
工厂方法，因为我被允许
put static factor
放置静态因子
on interfaces I can put it here
在接口上我可以把它放在这里
extractor this method returns a my
提取器此方法返回一个my
comparator of T since it is static I
T的比较器，因为它是静态的I
need to declare the type here and I am
需要在这里声明类型，我是
going to call it for instance comparing
将其称为例如比较
what's wrong with it yeah
怎么了耶
this should be it
应该是这样
so now I can my comparator is created by
所以现在我可以创建比较器了
calling this factory method my
将此工厂方法称为我的
comparator comparing last name I do not
比较器比较姓氏我不
need this static method here because
这里需要此静态方法，因为
I've moved it to the my compiler
我已经将其移至我的编译器中
interface and this last name is just
界面，这个姓氏就是
this lambda expression so I'm going to
这个lambda表达式，所以我要
ignite this and remove this and by the
点燃并移除此
way this time the expression can be
这次表达的方式
returned as an as a method reference my
作为方法参考返回
IDE can have been doing that person
IDE可能一直在做那个人
current count get last name it's just
当前计数获取姓氏
another syntax for method reference is
方法引用的另一种语法是
just another syntax to write our lambda
只是编写lambda的另一种语法
expressions and this is the final
表达式，这是最终的
pattern to create comparators using
模式以使用创建比较器
those factory methods and lambda
那些工厂方法和lambda
expressions if I check the code in fact
表达式，如果我实际上检查代码
all the creation of the compiled to
所有创建的编译到
itself using lambda is now in my API
我自己的API中现在使用lambda本身
instead of being in my application code
而不是在我的应用程序代码中
if I want to make this code robust by
如果我想通过以下方式使代码健壮
checking if last name is nil the first
检查姓氏是否为零
thing I should be doing of course is
我应该做的当然是
throw another experimental pointer
抛出另一个实验指针
exception if here by by the way I'm
例外，如果顺便说一句我在这里
going to call that extractor all right
会好好叫那个提取器
and if I want to check that last name
如果我想检查那个姓氏
they say this is s1 and this is s2 not
他们说这是s1，这不是s2
necessary the last name if I want to
如果我想的话，需要姓
check if s1 or s2 is near I can do it
检查s1或s2是否在我附近
inside my API without having to lower
在我的API中，而不必降低
the readability of my application code
我的应用程序代码的可读性
but what what I would like to do now is
但是我现在想做的是
go one step further and say alright if
再走一步说好吧
the last name the last name of my two
我两个的姓
people are the same then I want to
人是一样的，那么我想
compare using the first name for
使用名字比较
instance then
然后
person yet
人呢
first name what is the status of this
名这个的状态是什么
new method then compare well obviously
新方法然后比较明显
it is called on the comparator this is
它在比较器上被称为
okay so it is an instance method of the
好吧，这是一个实例方法
my comparator interface I fall back on
我的比较器接口
the same kind of question as previously
与以前一样的问题
there is the that we saw with my
有我们看到的
consumer of all my predicate so what I
我所有谓词的消费者，那么我
can do is create this then compare
可以做的就是创建这个然后比较
method as a default method of the my
方法作为my的默认方法
comparator interface it is going to take
比较器接口
the same kind of parameter as the
与
factory method comparing and returns
工厂方法比较并返回
also my comparator of T so let us do
也是我的T比较器，所以让我们做
that default as I said it returns my
我说的那个默认值返回我的
comparator of T it is called then
T的比较器称为
compare and takes a function that takes
比较并采用一个函数
two T returns the string Y now what I
两个T现在返回字符串Y
need to return them is a comparator the
需要将它们返回的是比较器
comparator is a functional interface and
比较器是一个函数式接口，
implementation of this method so once
这种方法的实现一次
again I'm doing the same thing
我又在做同样的事情
copy-paste this block of parameter then
复制并粘贴此参数块，然后
return an integer for instance one at
返回一个整数，例如在
least it should work and it doesn't now
至少它应该工作，现在不行
I need to be a little smarter than that
我需要比这更聪明
of course what should I be doing first I
当然我应该先做什么
need to compare the people using the
需要比较使用
comparator I mean so get the result of
比较器，我的意思是说得到
this compared T 1 and T 2
比较T 1和T 2
now if CMP is equal to zero then I need
现在，如果CMP等于零，那么我需要
to fall back on the comparator
落在比较器上
constructed using the past is a key
用过去建造是关键
extractor and if it's not the case I
提取器，如果不是这种情况，我
just return the value of CM
只需返回CM的值
this code is gone here I need to create
此代码消失了，我需要创建
another comparator using the past key
使用过去的密钥的另一个比较器
extractor there but I've got this
那里的提取器，但我有这个
factory method for that extractor this
该提取器的工厂方法
is my comparator of T I can call it
我的TI比较器可以称之为吗
other and just return the result of the
其他并返回结果
comparison using other okay so this is
比较使用其他的好吧，这是
an implementation a possible
一个可能的实现
implementation of the combination of two
两者结合实施
comparators created in two different key
用两个不同的键创建比较器
extractors by the way by the way I also
顺便提一下我也
need to protect myself against the
需要保护自己免受
psychopathic try to call me with an arc
精神病患者尝试用弧线给我打电话
extractor
提取器
this one should even be could even be
这个甚至应该是
written with the ternary operator
用三元运算符编写
kind of like the ternary operator it
有点像三元运算符
reminds me my old days of C programming
让我想起了我过去的C编程
so it simply is equal to zero what I
所以我等于零
returned in the company exactor which is
退回公司检察官
the comparator compared t 1 and t 2 and
比较器比较t 1和t 2以及
if it's not the case just CMP on this
如果不是这种情况，只需对此进行CMP
code
码
almost
几乎
what's wrong with you okay right this is
你怎么了，好吧，这是
nice so you see that we almost done with
很好，所以您看到我们几乎完成了
our program do you remember this large
我们的程序你还记得这么大吗
piece of unreadable crappy Java 7 blah
片不可读的烂Java 7等等
blah blah code showed you at the
等等等等代码向您展示了
beginning we almost we almost there we
开始我们几乎我们几乎在那里我们
almost there
快好了
we're not quite there because what I
我们不在那里，因为我
would like to do is compare it also
想做的就是比较一下
using person yet age and this one does
使用年龄的人，这个
not compile why because age is an
不编译为什么因为年龄是一个
integer and I wrote my code to take
整数，我写了代码
function that takes a string that
需要一个字符串的函数
written the string as a parameter so I
将字符串写为参数，所以我
need to deep dive into more generic hell
需要深入研究更一般的地狱
which is something that everybody loves
这是每个人都喜欢的东西
of course so I'm going to use a treat
当然，所以我要请客
for that right
为了那个权利
see how can I do it string here and I'm
看看我该怎么做在这里，我
going to go
要去
never tell anyone you saw me doing that
永远不要告诉任何人你看到我这样做
all right I'm gonna do the same here
好吧，我要在这里做同样的事情
encourage you so know what I'm basically
鼓励你，所以我基本上知道我
trying to do is okay this is not a
尝试做是好的，这不是一个
string this is any any kind of object of
字符串，这是任何类型的对象
type you so it will work now because
输入您的姓名，以便现在可以正常使用，因为
because this this code does compile but
因为这段代码可以编译，但是
the static that the factory method does
工厂方法执行的静态操作
not compile because on this you object I
无法编译，因为您对此表示反对
need is compared to method on it and
将需求与方法进行比较，并
this compare to method in fact is
这种与方法的比较实际上是
defined on the comparable interface so
在可比接口上定义，因此
you has to extend comparable and if you
你必须扩大可比性，如果你
want to make it correctly its comparable
想要正确地使其具有可比性
super you some kind of reason welcome to
超级你某种理由欢迎您
the generics paradise okay so if I if I
仿制药天堂好吧，如果我
do it like that now it would work and
这样就可以了，并且
code will compile because integer is a
代码将编译，因为整数是一个
comparable object and string is and now
可比较的对象和字符串是和现在
my comparator can be I could go even
我的比较者可以是我什至可以
even one step further like this by
像这样更进一步
telling okay now that I have this
现在告诉我我有这个
comparator in fact I want to sort my my
比较器实际上我想对我的排序
students in the other way around just by
学生反过来
calling the reversed on this on this
在这个上调用反向
comparator so reverse once again I think
比较器如此再次反转我认为
you've got the trick now it's also a
你现在有把戏了
default method of my compiler interface
我的编译器界面的默认方法
so let us write it and you see that it's
所以让我们写它，你会发现它是
going to be very easy in fact default
实际上很容易做到默认
takes my compiler of T returns ROI or my
让我的T编译器返回ROI或
compart of T this is the reversed method
与T比较的方法
does not take any parameter what is
不带任何参数是什么
return is a comparator so once again
返回是一个比较器，所以再次
implemented using a lambda and it
使用lambda实现，它
returns the the opposite of the result
返回结果的反面
of the comparison of t1 and t2 this
t1和t2的比较
compare
相比
you want to I can I have two tricks to
你想我有两个窍门
achieve that either I put a minus here
实现我在这里放减号
and it will reverse the comparison or if
它将颠倒比较或
I do not want to put the minus here I
我不想把减号放在这里
can just compare t2 and t1 to achieve
可以只比较t2和t1来实现
the same result sure yep - you don't do
同样的结果肯定是的-您不这样做
both because if you do both it will not
两者都是因为如果两者都做，将不会
work of course obviously but you can
当然可以工作，但是你可以
choose that I'm pretty sure that some of
选择我很确定
you are thinking is I think that if I
你在想我是否认为如果我
put the - it will be faster than if I
放-比我快
okay I don't know it's really up to you
好吧，我不知道这真的取决于你
yeah
是的
I could also treat other factory method
我也可以治疗其他工厂方法
on this comparator stuff for instance my
在这个比较器上的东西，例如我的
comparator string
比较器字符串
CMP - and I want to create my competitor
CMP-我想创建我的竞争对手
[Music]
[音乐]
because
因为
zero compared with your fancies to zero
零，而您的幻想为零
they say this is a this is a static
他们说这是一个静态
method can I create it yes I can model
我可以创建它的方法吗
and I'm going to return the comparator
我将返回比较器
string this one is to and return the
将此字符串发送到并返回
comparison of s1 with model for instance
s1与模型的比较
return sorry no so it doesn't make sense
返回抱歉，没有，所以没有道理
I'm messing up with a let us suppose
我想让我们搞砸了
yeah this is a string so let let us
是的，这是一个字符串，所以让我们
suppose that we just want to compare
假设我们只想比较
those strings using the natural order to
那些使用自然顺序的字符串
change sorry
改变对不起
so for the confusion I'm going to change
所以对于混乱我要改变
the example okay because the string is
这个例子还可以，因为字符串是
already a common of a comparable object
已经是可比较对象的共同点
so I can just use the natural order back
所以我可以使用自然顺序
and this is going to be something like
这将是像
that it's one that compared to and by
与之相比，
the way I can do it for any kind of
我可以做任何事情的方式
object that is comparable you extends
可扩展的对象
comparable
可比
I'm sorry yeah
对不起，是的
we're done
我们完成了
well you asked to exam sorry you asked
好，你问考试对不起，你问
to extends comparable because what I'm
扩展可比性，因为我
doing is using this compare to method
做的是使用此比较方法
which is precisely defined on the
正是在
comparable interface strain implements
可比的界面应变工具
comparable it was the same problem as
可比的是与
the as the previous one here when I went
和我去的时候一样
from the string to the to you if I do
从字符串到你到我
not say that you extends comparable that
并不是说您扩展了可比性
you fault back to object and I do not
你挑剔回到对象，我不
have this compared to never one object
与没有一个对象相比
this is why I can't use the comparative
这就是为什么我不能使用比较
method here I'm saying that you extends
这里的方法我是说你扩展
comparable and this comparable method
可比的和这种可比的方法
which is by the way functional interface
顺便说一下函数式接口
has the compareto method so it's another
有compareto方法，所以这是另一个
way of creating factory methods on the
在上创建工厂方法的方法
comparator interface yeah we can we can
比较器接口是的，我们可以
- we can take a very quick look on the
-我们可以快速浏览一下
comparator interface from the GDK eight
来自GDK的比较器接口八
it has the compareto method as usual and
它像往常一样具有compareto方法，
after that five hundred lines more than
在那五百行之后
five hundred lines of default and static
五百行默认和静态
method to create comparators using five
五种创建比较器的方法
methods and combine a combination of
方法，并结合在一起
them
他们
and okay so we saw how to use default
好的，所以我们看到了如何使用默认值
method to combine and to compose
组合和组成的方法
predicates and comparator so how to use
谓词和比较器，如何使用
factory method to create instances of
创建实例的工厂方法
lambda expressions without having any
没有任何lambda表达式
kind of complex stuff leaking in a coder
一种复杂的东西在编码器中泄漏
let us go one step further by the way
让我们更进一步
I've been using method references in my
我一直在使用方法引用
code I could show you other examples of
代码，我可以向您展示其他示例
that because we wrote lambdas that were
那是因为我们写的lambda
in fact method references this is a
实际上方法引用这是一个
method reference I have this magic
方法参考我有这个魔力
shortcut in Eclipse control 1 and if a
Eclipse控件1中的快捷方式，如果
lambda is a method reference you select
lambda是您选择的方法参考
it control 1 and it will give you the
它控制1，它将为您提供
possibility to directly make it make it
直接使其实现的可能性
a method reference this is also a
方法参考这也是
measure reference and guess what this
测量参考并猜测这是什么
one is too
一个也是
oh well this one is to my reference
哦，这是给我参考的
which is here right the next one is not
在这里，下一个不是
okay so there are four types of method
好，所以有四种方法
reference I've put them in this in this
参考我已经把他们放在这个
table
表
static bound instance unbound instance
静态绑定实例未绑定实例
and constructor will see constructor in
构造函数将在
a minute and I also gave you examples of
一分钟，我还给你举了一些例子
how to pass from a lambda to a method
如何从lambda传递给方法
reference in order for cases beside the
为了参考案例
slides will be variable slideshare I
幻灯片将是可变的slideshare I
guess you all know this book this is
猜猜你们都知道这本书是
called the Gang of Four it has a bunch
叫做“四人帮”，有一堆
of wonderful patterns in it we're not
的奇妙图案，我们不是
going to talk about all those patterns
要谈论所有这些模式
but what I would like to show you is
但我想告诉你的是
just a hint on how to implement some of
只是关于如何实施一些提示
those patterns using lambda expressions
使用lambda表达式的那些模式
default methods and factory methods in
中的默认方法和工厂方法
very efficient way that is begin with
非常有效的方法
the factory pattern I love this one the
我喜欢这个的工厂模式
factory
厂
close this so I've created a class that
关闭这个，所以我创建了一个类
is a factory it doesn't do much for the
是一家工厂，对工厂没有多大帮助
moment is it the one I want to use I'm
现在是我要使用的那个
going to use this this little class so
打算用这个小班
what is the factory well I do I want to
我想做什么工厂好
create a factory
建立工厂
I have several several other objects in
我还有其他几个对象
my in my model package here a shape a
我在我的模型包中的形状是
shape object which is just an abstract
形状对象只是一个抽象
shape there's nothing in it the circle
形状里面没有东西
class that extends shape with two
用两个形状扩展的类
constructor that takes one that is empty
需要一个空的构造函数
and another one that takes a color and
另一种颜色
also a square and a triangle class to
还有一个正方形和一个三角形类
use how should I be using a factory
使用我应该如何使用工厂
object this is my factory if I want to
如果我想反对，这是我的工厂
create a factory of circle so called
创建一个所谓的圆形工厂
factory basically what I expect from
工厂基本上是我期望的
this factory of circle I don't know how
这个不知道怎么办的工厂
to create it but what I expect this from
创建它，但是我期望从中得到什么
this factory to be able to call a method
这个工厂可以调用方法
suppose a get method that is going to
假设要使用的get方法
return so they say this is the basic
返回，所以他们说这是基本的
pattern of how to use a factory now if I
如果我现在如何使用工厂的模式
take a look at this code if I take a
看一下这段代码，如果我
look at this code from the from the
从中看这段代码
lambda perspective this get method here
Lambda透视图，这里的get方法
doesn't take any parameter and does
不带任何参数，而是
return an object so if you remember the
返回一个对象，所以如果您还记得
four categories of lambda expression I
lambda表达式四类我
have this is a supplier it doesn't take
有这个供应商，不需要
anything creates an object so it means
任何东西都会创建一个对象，所以这意味着
that my factory here is in fact not
我的工厂实际上不在
necessary a class could be an interface
一个类可能是一个接口
that extends
延伸
supplier of tea and supply of cheese
茶和奶酪的供应商
very nice because it has a get method
非常好，因为它具有get方法
that does not take anything that and
那并不需要任何东西
that creates something so if I want to
这会产生一些东西，所以如果我想
create an implementation of that Factory
创建该工厂的实现
so we the same I just take a block of
所以我们还是一样
parameters and what should I return well
参数，我应该返回什么
a new circle
一个新圈子
so basically this is a factory from the
所以基本上这是一家工厂
Gulf implemented using lambdas in July
海湾地区在7月使用Lambda实施
and by the way this is also a
顺便说一句，这也是
constructor method reference that I came
我来的构造方法参考
that I can write in this way what could
我可以这样写
I do with this factory well I could for
我可以很好地与这家工厂合作
instance say ok so a factory
举例说，好吧，工厂
give me five circles in list
在清单上给我五个圆圈
five circles
五圈
what is this get method it's not the
这是什么get方法，不是
same as the get method that does not
与不使用的get方法相同
take any argument it's a method defined
接受任何参数，这是定义的方法
on the instance of the factory so once
以工厂为例，所以一次
again this is a default method okay so I
再次，这是默认方法，所以我
can create here a default method you
可以在这里创建默认方法
treat on the list of T it takes an
在T列表上对待
integer let us make it written your list
整数，让我们将其写入您的列表
just to have it compile this is a list
只是要编译这是一个列表
and this is in your list and that's it
这是在您的列表中，仅此而已
at least it compile now what should I be
至少现在编译我应该是什么
doing in this create five circles and
在此过程中创建五个圈子，
put them in a list I could create a
将它们放在列表中，我可以创建一个
follow-up but I am using Java 8 so I've
跟进，但我使用Java 8，所以我已经
got this nice in stream object then can
得到了这个不错的流对象然后可以
create a stream of n integers for me I
为我创建n个整数流
can map the stream to object take the
可以将流映射到对象
index return and you saw new sorry
索引返回，您看到了新的抱歉
return a new instance of what this
返回这个的新实例
Factory can create that is called a
工厂可以创建一个称为
stopgap method could put this here right
权宜之计可以将其放在此处
and put the result list
并放入结果列表
and just return that for loops are so
只是返回for循环是如此
Java 8
Java 8
Java 7 sorry okay so this is just one
Java 7对不起，所以这只是一个
line to to to to create this thing and
线到创建这个东西，
if I run this code with factories
如果我在工厂运行此代码
five circles for each system that out
每个系统五个圈
printer n code and get all my five
打印机N代码，并得到我所有的五个
circles created using this default
使用此默认设置创建的圈子
method now I have another constructor is
现在我有另一个构造函数的方法是
my in my circle which is a circle that
我在我的圈子中
takes a color as a parameter so suppose
假设颜色是参数
I want to what I would like to do now is
我现在想做的是
to create for instance red red circles
例如创建红色红色圆圈
red circles factory doesn't take
红圈工厂不带
anything and you so call this is the
任何东西，你称之为这是
create way to code just copy paste this
创建代码的方式只是复制粘贴
code five this is five red circle run
代码五这是五个红色圆圈
this code and then if I run this code I
这段代码，然后如果我运行这段代码，
have first five normal circles and then
先有五个正常的圈子，然后
five red circles so from from a factory
来自工厂的五个红色圆圈
I can add as many default method as I as
我可以添加尽可能多的默认方法
I need to create more stuff to add
我需要创建更多东西来添加
functionalities to my to my factory
我到我工厂的功能
which is nice what is not that nice is
哪个好不是那个好
the way this code is written here
此代码的编写方式
because in fact what I what I'm doing
因为事实上我在做什么
here is it's putting inside the supplier
这是放在供应商内部
parameter that I would like to pass as a
我想作为一个参数传递
parameter to another method in fact I
参数实际上是另一种方法
would not not I'm not too happy with
会不会，我不太满意
this code I better write it like that
这段代码我最好这样写
I prefer write it like that Factory and
我更喜欢像Factory这样写
say okay I passed the constructor as a
说好吧，我将构造函数作为
parameter new so-called of color and
参数新所谓的颜色和
then pass the color also as a parameter
然后将颜色也作为参数传递
okay this is what I would like to do
好的，这就是我想做的
Factory and pass it for instance or
工厂并通过例如
factory method to the to the factory
工厂方法到工厂
class itself so this create method here
类本身，所以这里的创建方法
with a static method of the factory
用工厂的静态方法
class we've been doing that to return
我们一直在做的课，以返回
the factory the factory it takes what is
工厂需要的工厂是
this it takes a car as a parameter and
这以汽车为参数，
return this code zero so this is a
返回此代码零，所以这是一个
function takes an object return an
函数需要一个对象返回
object of a node type create takes a
节点类型创建的对象需要一个
function we are going to make it with
我们将要实现的功能
this is a factory circle right so I'm
这是一个工厂界，所以我
going to write it like that it should be
打算这样写
easier
更轻松
it takes a color as a parameter and the
它使用颜色作为参数，
circle my circle and this is in fact my
圈我一圈，这实际上是我的
constructor and take a color as a
构造函数并将颜色作为
parameter and it should be I'm going to
参数，应该是我要
return there here and it should it
回到这里，应该
should return and this should return the
应该返回，这应该返回
factory that is something that doesn't
工厂是没有的
take any argument and returns a factory
接受任何论点并返回工厂
of circle so for that I need to in fact
圈，因此我实际上需要
take my constructor and apply the color
带上我的构造函数并应用颜色
to that function here what I did is a
在这里我要做的是一个
very important portent operation I took
我进行的非常重要的预备手术
a function and made it the supplier by
一个功能，并使其成为供应商
fixing the parameter of that function
固定该函数的参数
right and this is the second fundamental
对，这是第二个基本原则
operation in functional programming the
功能编程中的操作
first one is composition and the second
第一个是组成，第二个
one is partial application what I've
一种是我的部分应用
done here is a partial application on
在这里完成的是部分应用
function to lower the number of
减少数量的功能
parameters that function take dates
带有日期的参数
since this function take takes only one
因为此功能只需要一个
parameter blowing it give me a supplier
参数吹给我一个供应商
and this
和这个
exactly what I did so now my factory can
正是我现在所做的，我的工厂可以
be returned I that it's still working by
返回我仍然在工作
the way okay which is great and since
好的，这很好，因为
this is also a method reference I can
这也是我可以的方法参考
write it like that and it gives me a
这样写，它给了我一个
very clean pattern because if I if I
非常干净的图案，因为如果我
compare the two patterns here I've got
比较这里的两种模式
this circled column column new on both
这圈圈列列新
on both sides even if it does not
即使没有
represent the same thing this is some
代表同一件事，这是一些
kind of trap with method references is
带有方法引用的陷阱是
that if you do not know the type of a
如果您不知道类型
method reference you cannot really know
您无法真正知道的方法参考
what is this method reference exactly
该方法的确切参考是什么
you see here I've got a method reference
你看这里我有一个方法参考
that is the supplier and here this is
那是供应商，这是
the same method reference the same
相同的方法引用相同
string of characters for the reference
供参考的字符串
but it's a function it's not the same
但这是一个功能，它是不一样的
type and it does not do the same thing
类型，它不会做同样的事情
right if I control click on this new
正确，如果我控制点击此新按钮
here it will take me to the empty
在这里它将带我空虚
constructor of the circle doesn't take
圆的构造函数不需要
any parameter written something this is
任何参数写的东西是
a supplier and if I check this other
供应商，如果我检查其他
method reference here if I control click
如果我控制点击，方法参考在这里
on this new object here a new code here
在这个新对象上，这里是新代码
it takes me to the constructor that
它带我到构造函数
takes a parameter because the type of
接受一个参数，因为
this method reference is not the same
这个方法参考不一样
okay how do I know that it's not the
好吧，我怎么知道这不是
same because this create method here
一样，因为这里的创建方法
takes a function and not to survive this
需要一个功能而不是为了生存
is whatever the trick is so be careful
到底是什么招要小心
with those metal references
与那些金属参考
okay I think we're done with the factory
好吧，我认为我们已经完成了工厂
that's on ya the next pattern I would
那是在下一个模式，我会
like to show you is the registry and
想要表明您是注册表，
under builder pattern the register
在建造者模式下登记
button is a very nice pattern
按钮是一个非常好的模式
yeah demo time once again so this time
是的演示时间再次如此
what I want to do is to create a
我想做的是创建一个
registry fact a factory that will create
注册表事实将创建的工厂
instances of objects with providing some
提供一些对象的实例
kind of key to say alright what I want
可以说我想要什么的钥匙
is a circle what I want is a triangle
是一个圆，我想要的是一个三角形
what I want is a square something like
我想要的是一个类似正方形的东西
that if I if I do this kind of thing I
如果我做这种事，
probably end up writing this kind of
可能最终会写这种
code switch key if my key is a circle
代码切换键（如果我的键是一个圆圈）
that I know what I want to do is to
我知道我想做的是
return I'm returning a factory right new
我要归还新工厂
circle if what I'm getting is a triangle
如果我得到的是一个三角形则圈一下
I want to return a factory triangle it's
我想返回一个工厂三角形
this one and if I get a square or I want
这个，如果我有一个正方形，或者我想要
to return
返回
he's a square
他是一个正方形
it should be a shape if I want the under
如果我想要下面它应该是一个形状
default right the default and if I don't
默认权默认值，如果我不这样做
have anything what I want to do is to
有什么我想做的就是
throw a new illegal argument exception
抛出新的非法论证异常
there's nothing
什么也没有
that's one beer factory of shape
那是一家啤酒厂
Meishan this one
眉山这一个
okay
好的
so this is something okay and I'm going
所以这没关系，我要去
to yeah so here I've got so this is this
是的，所以在这里我有这个
one so here I want to create my shape
所以在这里我要创造我的形状
factory ship back to your shape shape
工厂运送回您的形状
factor in equals new shape factory right
等于新形状工厂的权利
and if I call shape factory so create
如果我叫形状工厂，那么创建
circle each returns up yes I got to draw
将每个圆圈圈起来，是的，我要画画
over the shape here it's not a right
在这里的形状是不正确的
shape the shape are created okay so this
形状创建好了，所以这
is my my my circle factory factory
是我我的圈子工厂
and I want to cast that into a factory
我想把它丢进工厂
of circle since what I get is in fact a
因为我得到的实际上是一个
factory machine
工厂机器
right
对
happy we did
我们很高兴
okay like that yes I've got this funny
好吧，像这样，我很有趣
warning so let us get rid of this with
警告，让我们摆脱与
this kind of magic hack provided by the
这种由
GDK suppress warning unchecked yes I
GDK取消警告未选中，是的，我
know what I'm doing okay so this is this
知道我在做什么，所以这是这个
is basically the registry pattern as we
基本上是我们的注册表模式
all saw it in our application might be
所有人在我们的应用程序中看到的可能是
not in this exact form but basically
不是以这种确切的形式，而是基本上
this is this is what what we what we can
这就是我们所能做到的
do you see that this registry pattern
你看到这个注册表模式吗
well can can be created on a way we
可以用一种方式创造好
creat the factory in the previous
在之前的工厂中创建
example which is which is basically this
基本上是这个的例子
one by the way if I want to create a
一个，如果我想创建一个
single home for instance I want to
例如我想要的一个家
return all the way the same triangle
一路返回相同的三角形
here if I'm with this with this factory
如果我在这家工厂的话
I am returning a new triangle every time
我每次都会返回一个新的三角形
I'm calling this Factory
我叫这个工厂
but if I want to make it a single tone I
但是如果我想让它变成单音
could
可以
just create a triangle as a private this
只是创建一个三角形作为私人
oh this is not static so I can do it
哦，这不是静态的，所以我可以做到
like that triangle equals new triangle
像那个三角形等于新三角形
and with the strake return always the
而随着走板收益总是
same triangle with my supplier this
与我的供应商相同的三角形
would be an implementation of the
将是
singleton pattern as a singleton pattern
单例模式作为单例模式
might not be the best pattern of the
可能不是最好的模式
world but you can still implement it
世界，但您仍然可以实现它
using using this kind of a blonde
使用这种金发女郎
expression what is not that great with
表达什么不是那么好
this way of writing things is that what
这种写东西的方式是
is not as great that grid is that if I
网格不是那么好，如果我
want to add them stuff to my to my to my
想要将它们添加到我到我的
registry I need to modify this code
注册表我需要修改此代码
recompile it recompile all my life my
重新编译它重新编译我一生
application and everywhere I I need to
应用程序和需要II的任何地方
do I'm using this registry we rewrite my
我正在使用此注册表我们重写我的
code everywhere so did this is not very
代码无处不在，这不是很好
how could I say that very very dynamic
我怎么能说非常非常有活力
way of funding registries what I what
注册管理机构的方式我是什么
most of the time people do to fix that
大多数情况下，人们会这样做
is to use a bingo pattern okay I've got
是要用宾果图案
to builder here which is the class this
到这里的建设者是这个类
builder pattern works in two steps first
构建器模式首先需要两个步骤
step I add elements to my registry and
步骤我将元素添加到注册表中，
then second step I use my registry as it
然后第二步，我使用我的注册表
is by calling the big method and using
是通过调用big方法并使用
this Jai factory we can just yeah
这个Jai工厂，我们可以
I'm going to put this one here
我要把这个放在这里
so I can how can I use this builder
所以我可以如何使用这个生成器
pattern but so many builders where where
模式，但很多建设者在哪里
is minor thanks here
是次要的感谢
right a builder so it's a bit of what
对一个建筑商来说，这有点
it's a bit of shape new bidder
有点像新的投标人
okay so in a first step I'm going to add
好的，所以第一步我要添加
a so called I'm the factory of circle
所谓的我是圈子的工厂
which is so called you and the same for
所谓的你和
triangle
三角形
Thank You clips do zero later later
谢谢剪辑稍后再做零
don't there's another triangle and the
没有另一个三角形，
same four square
相同的四个正方形
just like that and now that my builder
就像那样，现在我的建造者
is done I just called the big stuff the
完成了，我只是把大东西叫做
build method on it to create my shell
在其上构建方法以创建我的外壳
Factory and from that chip factory I
工厂和那个芯片工厂
will be able to create my factories and
将能够创建我的工厂，
use my factories as I mean this is by
用我的工厂，因为我的意思是
the way a pattern that has been used in
模式的使用方式
industry maybe I itself if I check the
行业本身，如果我检查
stream interface I've got a builder a
流接口，我有一个生成器
member interface that extends consumer
扩展消费者的成员接口
in which I can add elements to it I add
我可以在其中添加元素
elements to that builder once this is
这是该构建器的元素
done I just got the Builder method on
完成，我刚刚获得了Builder方法
that builder to get to create the stream
该构建器可以创建流
with all the elements I have added to
加上我添加到的所有元素
the bidder the problem is that once I
投标人的问题是，一旦我
have called the build method I cannot
已经调用了我无法建立的方法
call them the add method anymore so this
称他们为add方法了，所以这
object has to remember state ok I am in
对象必须记住状态好，我在
the build mode I think it amounts to my
我认为构建模式相当于我的
builder and then I have created the
生成器，然后我创建了
object I was building so I'm out of the
我正在建造的物体，所以我不在
build mode and it's somebody caused the
构建模式，有人造成了
add object again I should raise an
再次添加对象，我应该提出一个
exception or something like that for an
例外或类似的东西
exception to tell the people a this this
告诉别人这个的例外
builder is done you cannot add any more
构建器完成，您无法再添加
elements to it so if I if I come back to
元素，所以如果我回到
my pattern I've got in fact the exact
我的模式我实际上有确切的
same problem in this pattern is that
这种模式的相同问题是
once I have called this bill method here
一旦我在这里调用此账单方法
I need to create some kind of internal
我需要创建某种内部
mechanism to make sure that nobody is
确保没有人是的机制
going to add any more object to this
要为此添加更多对象
builder and this may be quite complex
建设者，这可能很复杂
first you need to to write this code
首先，您需要编写这段代码
which is not that simple
这不是那么简单
and second you need to think that other
其次，您需要考虑其他
people can can access using reflection
人们可以使用反射进行访问
to your internal registry other threads
到您的内部注册表其他线程
could be doing the same also so you need
可能也一样，所以你需要
to handle all these kind of cases if you
处理所有这类情况，如果您
do not want to have any bugs in your
不想在您的任何错误
application they say this is not that
他们说这不是那个应用
great now how can we
现在好极了
make this make this pattern better
使这个使这个模式更好
precisely using numbers first what we
首先要精确地使用数字
can see is that this shape factory here
可以看到的是这里的形状工厂
as only in fact one method to implement
因为实际上只有一种实现方法
here and when you have a class that has
在这里，当你有一堂课
only one method to implement you should
只有一种方法可以实现
have something in your mind telling you
你心里有话要告诉你
oh maybe I could make it an interface
哦，也许我可以使其成为一个界面
and implement that using the lambda
并使用lambda实现
because most of the time it's possible
因为大多数时候都有可能
I'm going to call this shape Factory
我将这个形状称为工厂
need to rename it legacy legacy shape
需要重命名它遗留的遗留形状
Factory and I'm going to create another
工厂，我要创建另一个
shape factory as an interface
形状工厂作为界面
and I'm just keeping the same method
我只是保持相同的方法
here thank you
在这里谢谢你
are you like that
你这样吗
you can see that this code is still
您可以看到此代码仍然
still compiling by the way yes because
还是顺便编译是的，因为
it's now built on sheer factory
它现在建立在纯粹的工厂上
it keeps please
它保持请
what is he doing doesn't want to import
他在做什么不想导入
refactoring
重构
trusting okay this is do it by him
相信这是他做的
oh yes is some public sorry okay and
哦，是一些公众对不起吗，
this bit that bill is going to return
这笔账单将要归还
the ship factory yes okay so my shape
船厂是好的，所以我的形状
factor is now is now and now I need to
因素是现在是现在，现在我需要
face and I'm going to implement it using
面对，我将使用
a lumber now what is this admitted going
一名木材现在承认这是怎么回事
to do well it will have to put this in
要做好，就必须把它放进去
some kind of registry so let us create
某种注册表，让我们创建
that map this is the natural way of
那是自然的方式
doing it's a map of stranger and factory
这样做是陌生人和工厂的地图
of T registry when you wash map ok and
洗地图确定时T注册表的内容和
what I'm going to do is just add this
我要做的就是添加这个
registry put yes key and now when I'm
注册表把是关键，现在当我
building this stuff what I need to
建立我需要的东西
return is a shape factory
回报是一个形状工厂
what is this shape factory it's an
这个形状工厂是什么
interface that is functional so it can
功能正常的界面
be implemented using lambda how can i
使用lambda实现我如何
implement it implemented using a lambda
使用lambda实现
just copy paste the block of parameter
只需复制粘贴参数块
and from that key I need to get the
从那个钥匙我需要得到
factory that is here because this sorry
工厂在这里，因为这很抱歉
this implementation returns a factory
此实现返回工厂
and the factories in the map so do this
还有地图上的工厂
kind of thing registry but get
有点东西注册表，但得到
troubles with the generic stuff man
与通用的东西麻烦
excuse me
劳驾
make it what it's me to try to the final
尝试决赛是我的一切
okay so in fact this bill method is just
好的，所以实际上这个账单方法只是
I'm going to to make it like that you
我要像你一样
see I'm going to copy paste this code
看到我要复制粘贴此代码
repeat here because in fact this code is
在这里重复，因为实际上这段代码是
a method reference it's just a get
方法引用，这只是一个获取
method of my register and this this is
我的注册方法，这是
what it is in fact to Bill do it Chester
比尔做切斯特实际上是什么
it's just a registry and when I create
这只是一个注册表，当我创建
the stuff I'm just giving it to this map
我只是给这张地图的东西
but I'm still not quite happy with the
但是我还是不太满意
code because here I have some code that
代码，因为这里有一些代码
is going to call add multiple times and
将要多次调用添加，
to cook that can be interrupted that can
做饭可以打断
be made multi-threaded that can subject
被制成多线程
to reflection it's not it's not that
反思不是，不是
great but if I check what does this code
很好，但是如果我检查这段代码是什么
do in fact and I'm going to use the same
实际上，我将使用相同的
trick I use to show you how the
我用来告诉你的技巧
comparator was made if I extract this
如果我提取这个比较器
code to this to a method or what I see
对此方法或我看到的代码
is that in fact it's a piece of code
实际上是一段代码
that takes a builder as a parameter and
将构建器作为参数，
does not return anything so in a sense
在某种意义上不返回任何东西
what is this piece of code take
这一段代码需要做什么
something does not return anything
东西什么都不会返回
it's itself a lambda expression that is
它本身就是一个lambda表达式
a consumer right so in fact all this
消费者的权利，所以事实上这一切
code can be returned as a consumer let's
代码可以作为消费者返回
do that it's a consumer of what the
这样做是什么的消费者
consumer vinda okay consumer of builder
消费者vinda好的建筑商的消费者
of shape let's call it consumer for the
我们称其为消费者
moment it takes a builder as a parameter
将构建器作为参数的瞬间
I'm just going to write it below like
我只是要像下面这样写
that and does this here I can get rid of
那并且做到这一点我可以摆脱
this method I do not need it anymore
这种方法我不再需要了
and now the nice stuff is I do not need
现在好东西是我不需要
that bit anymore I do not need a builder
那一点我不再需要建造者
in
在
my application code to initialize a
我的应用程序代码初始化一个
builder and you have created the model
生成器，您已经创建了模型
of initialization and this is a very
初始化，这是一个非常
very general pattern in fact the process
其实很普通的过程
of finishing an object using a builder
使用构建器完成对象的过程
is basically a consumer so you can write
基本上是消费者，所以你可以写
this consumer pass this consumer this
这个消费者通过这个消费者
extracted stuff passed this consumer to
提取的东西通过了这个消费者
a factoring method of our builder
我们的构建者的分解方法
interface builder create pass this
界面生成器创建通过此
consumer as a parameter and now what I
消费者作为参数，现在我
expect to have as a returned object is a
期望作为返回对象是
bigger object that is both created and
既创建又更大的对象
initialized with the consumer I have
用我有的消费者初始化
provided ok so what is this method
提供确定，这是什么方法
obviously it's a static method on my
显然，这是我的静态方法
builder interface public static or did I
构建器接口public static还是我
call it create texture consumer as a
称之为创建纹理消费者
parameter returns a builder okay with of
参数返回可以的构建器
T I need to tell the acidity create and
TI需要告诉其酸度
take the consumer of builder of T as a
将T制造商的消费者视为
parameter and this is my initializer
参数，这是我的初始值设定项
let us return you to see if we got it
让我们返回您，看看是否收到
right I think so all right so now in
是的，我想现在可以了
this static method what I had to have is
我必须要使用的静态方法是
create this builder new bidder
创建此建造者新的投标人
okay and pass this bitter as a parameter
好的，将此苦味作为参数传递
to the initializer we just passed like
到我们刚刚传递的初始化程序
that and return this builder okay so you
然后返回这个生成器，好吧，你
see that now I mean I'm in a better
看到现在我的意思是我处在一个更好的状态
shape than previously because I cannot
形状比以前因为我不能
interrupt the process between the
中断之间的过程
construction of the object and its
对象的构造及其
initialization so it's not possible to
初始化，所以不可能
interact it anymore but I can go even
不再互动了，但我什至可以
even further because now I'm just
更进一步，因为现在我只是
calling this create factor in the other
在另一个中称这个创造因素
so this build method here is not used
所以这里不使用这种构建方法
anymore I can just get rid of it okay
我现在可以摆脱它了
and what I see here is that I have only
我在这里看到的是，我只有
one method in my video object well if I
如果我可以在视频对象中使用一种方法
have only one method that probably means
只有一种方法可能意味着
that one I mean one instance method if I
那是我的意思是一个实例方法
have only one method in my video object
我的视频对象中只有一种方法
probably means that I can make it an
可能意味着我可以做到
interface and make this method abstract
界面并使该方法抽象
that I'm going to comment out this code
我要注释掉这段代码
make this method abstract and make my
使此方法抽象并使我的
glitter an interface now of course this
现在闪闪发光的界面
registry here cannot be an instance
这里的注册表不能是实例
failure of an interface I cannot create
我无法创建的接口故障
this builder like that anymore because
这样的建造者，因为
it's another object but this is a lambda
这是另一个对象，但这是一个lambda
so I can implement it just using an
所以我可以使用
implementation
实作
of this abstract method here so let us
这里的这种抽象方法
do that I just copy paste always the
我只是总是复制粘贴
same principle I just copy paste block
同样的原则，我只是复制粘贴块
of parameter and what should I be doing
参数，我应该怎么做
with that doing registry dot put key and
与做注册表点把钥匙和
factory this registry cannot be created
工厂无法创建此注册表
as a field but it can be created as the
作为字段，但可以将其创建为
local variable alright so first I create
好了，所以我首先创建
my registry then I create my builder
我的注册表，然后创建我的生成器
third step I initialize my builder using
第三步，使用
a consumer and then I return it and this
消费者，然后我将其退回
piece of code here is in fact a method
这段代码实际上是一种方法
reference I'm going to keep that so if I
参考我会保留，所以如果我
really want to make my code completely
真的很想让我的代码完全
unreadable I can just write it like that
不可读我可以这样写
okay
好的
okay okay so you see that using this
好吧好吧，所以你看到使用这个
kind of code I can go really very
我可以非常非常喜欢的一种代码
further with only very simple principles
仅用非常简单的原理
that is try to get to to to understand
那是试图去了解
where the lambdas are when I have a
当我有一个lambda时
class with only one method have in mind
只考虑一种方法的类
that I can implement that class well I
我可以很好地实施该课程
can make an interface with that class
可以与该类建立接口
and implement it with a lambda and you
并用lambda实现它
see that here I'm a very better shape
看到这里我的状态更好
much better shape than than I used to be
形状比以前好得多
in the previous example okay in the
在前面的示例中，
first step I had the creation of an
第一步，我创建了一个
object in a class the registry was a
类中的对象注册表是一个
field of that class remember here this
那个班级的人记得这里
was a field of that class anybody could
是那个阶级的领域，任何人都可以
have access using reflection to the feet
可以反射到脚
of that class meaning that could that I
该类的意思是说
could correct my code with reflection or
可以用反射来纠正我的代码或
concurrency or thing like that now my
并发或类似的东西现在我
registry is completely hidden it's a
注册表是完全隐藏的
local variable in a static interface so
静态接口中的局部变量
nobody can see it even using reflection
连反射都没人看
I do not have to use a concurrent - map
我不必使用并发-映射
here because this code will be executed
在这里，因为此代码将被执行
just by one single thread you can have a
只需一个线程，您就可以拥有一个
local variable shared I'm afraid this is
局部变量共享，恐怕这是
not possible so this code is both much
不可能，所以这段代码很多
more robust much less error-prone than
更加健壮，比发生错误的可能性要小得多
the previous one it might not be that
上一个可能不是
simple - right I agree but it's still
简单-对，我同意，但仍然
very
非常
right and I think I'm done with it
对，我想我已经完成了
yeah
是的
all right
好吧
so this is my confusions my confusion
所以这是我的困惑我的困惑
you see that lambdas expression alumni
你看到那个lambdas表情的校友
expressions have been presented as a
表达式已表示为
nicer way to write instances of
编写实例的更好的方法
anonymous classes and default methods
匿名类和默认方法
have been presented also as as a way to
也作为一种方式提出
modify existing interfaces without
修改现有接口而无需
changing classes this was useful to know
换班这很有用
when Java it was new this is not the
当Java是新的，这不是
case anymore time a nine is there by the
情况再一次，那边有一个9
way and in several years from now nobody
从现在开始的几年内
will remember what it was before it
会记得之前的事
what will stay I think is that we have a
我想我会留下的是
new model of function in Java which is
Java中新的函数模型
called a functional interface with two
称为具有两个函数式接口
possibilities composition given by
给出的可能性组成
default method partial applications
默认方法部分应用
which is the second fundamental
这是第二个基本要素
operation in functional programming and
功能编程中的操作和
also factory methods to create easily
也可以轻松创建工厂方法
lambda expression using using parameters
使用参数使用lambda表达式
so this is really a new way of creating
所以这真的是一种新的创造方式
applications and implementing patterns
应用程序和实施模式
and I think it's a very nice addition to
而且我认为这是非常不错的补充
our applications and an API this is what
我们的应用程序和API，这就是
I wanted to tell you today thank you for
我今天想告诉你，谢谢
your attention
你的注意力
and I think we have some time for
我认为我们有一些时间
questions do we yeah yeah yeah if you
问题是吗，是的，如果你
should just google my account on
应该只是谷歌我的帐户
SlideShare you'll find it
SlideShare您会发现它
yes I can push my code record in Mario
是的，我可以在Mario中推送代码记录
github accounts okay do some maybe do
github帐户好吧做一些也许
some cleaning referred any other
其他一些清洁服务
questions yes please sorry you have to
问题是，请您对不起
specify the type yes now it's optional
指定类型，现在是可选的
when you write your lambda extra it's
当您额外编写lambda时，
really a matter of readability if you
如果你真的是一个可读性问题
think that Jo code is more readable by
认为Jo代码更易于阅读
specifying the code if it helps you just
指定代码是否对您有帮助
do it there's no difference in the way
做到这一点没有什么区别
the code is compiled and the performance
代码被编译并且性能
of the code executed so it's just a
所执行的代码，所以这只是一个
matter it's the same for lambdas versus
重要的是，lambda与
method references if you're more
方法参考，如果您更多
comfortable with lambda just just keep
对lambda感到满意，只是保持
you along the new code and as time goes
随着时间的推移，您会遵循新的代码
by you'll probably become used to to
通过你可能会习惯
method references I'd like to write you
我想给你写的方法引用
a video using them but the compiled code
使用它们但已编译的代码的视频
is the same so there's no difference in
是一样的，所以没有区别
performance between metal reference in
金属参考之间的性能
London questions yeah there is an
伦敦问，有一个
excellent book by written by Maurice
莫里斯写的好书
naphthalene the bad lambdas on stream
萘流中的坏λ
there I do not know of any book
那里我什么都不知道
especially on lambdas only on lambdas
特别是在lambda上，仅在lambdas上
they usually cover lambdas the new
他们通常会覆盖新的Lambda
methods on the collection framework
收集框架上的方法
streams and characters and I think the
流和字符，我认为
the one written by Morrison after is
莫里森之后写的是
excellent it's available in the library
很好，可以在图书馆找到
and there's also Java in action yeah
还有Java在起作用
you cannot switch on a class name the
你不能打开一个类名
switch the switch only takes primitive
切换只需原始
time integers enumerations and strings
时间整数枚举和字符串
you cannot provide a class in a switch
您不能在交换机中提供课程
statement so you have to provide a key
声明，因此您必须提供一个密钥
which may be the class name or any kind
可以是类名或任何种类
of label that would represent the class
代表班级的标签
there are other ways to implement this
还有其他方法可以实现
pattern you can also implement it using
模式，您也可以使用
your using a numeration for instance
您例如使用数字
first get get the animator set values
首先获取获得动画师的设置值
value that you that you need and then
珍惜您需要的东西，然后
call an instance method and that
调用一个实例方法
enumerated value that will give you the
枚举值，将为您提供
right Factory no it's not the only way
正确的工厂，这不是唯一的方法
to do it but this one the one I should
做到这一点，但我应该做到这一点
have I think is the the most classical
我认为最经典的
way of implementing it yeah
实现它的方式
yep
是的
I'm not sure quite get your question
我不太确定你的问题
sorry yeah
对不起
yeah
是的
yeah usually when you're using a
是的，通常当您使用
dependency injection framework you can
您可以依赖注入框架
also provide factory methods to create
还提供工厂方法来创建
your objects whether it's in spring or
您的对象，无论是春季还是春季
in CDI for instance
例如在CDI中
so just by annotating the right pieces
所以只要注释正确的部分
of code around so if you so you can see
代码的周围，所以如果您可以看到
do that and the yes leverage leverage
做到这一点，是的杠杆杠杆
lambda but the dependency injection
lambda但依赖项注入
framework will will create proxies on
框架将创建代理
objects so if you're using lambdas in
对象，因此，如果您在使用lambda
them Yolanda's will be kind of cluttered
他们约兰达的会有点混乱
with all those proxies and you will lose
所有这些代理，您将输掉
most of the most of the good things you
大部分最美好的事物
will have when using just plain lambda
仅使用普通lambda时将具有
basically lambdas is not implemented as
基本上lambdas没有实现为
an object inside the JVM which if she
JVM中的一个对象，如果她
were calling the two strings or equals
正在调用两个字符串或等于
of the object methods on a lambda which
lambda上的对象方法
which is still possible because it will
这仍然是可能的，因为它将
compile then you are you are losing all
编译那么你就是你正在失去所有
the the optimization the JVM will be
JVM的优化
able to set up for you in a way when
能够以某种方式为您设置
you're just using plain lambda so if
你只是用普通的lambda，所以如果
you're using plain lambdas just just use
您正在使用纯lambda，而只是使用
them as is do not do any funny stuff
他们照原样做任何有趣的事情
with them yeah
和他们在一起
I'd never I did not heard of any I don't
我从来没有听说过我没有
I don't think it has I can't be exactly
我不认为我不能完全
sure that there is room for improvement
确保有改进的空间
the wait lambdas have been implemented
等待lambda已实施
in the JDM there is room for improvement
在JDM中，还有改进的空间
in the future I am Not sure there are
将来我不确定
they were major modification on that
他们是对此的重大修改
field any other questions okay thank you
现场还有其他问题好吗谢谢
for your attention
为了您的关注
have a great day
祝你有美好的一天
[Applause]
[掌声]